Robert C. Hendrickson Papers
Robert C. Hendrickson Papers
- Communications and writings
  - Correspondence
    - Gea-Gev, 1939-1953 (Box 16)
    - Gib-Giu, 1947-1962 (Box 17)
    - Gla-Gou, 1937-1962 (Box 17)
    - Gra-Gro, 1937-1962 (Box 17)
    - Gue-Gru, 1937-1954 (Box 17)
    - Galloway, George B., 1952-1954 (Box 17)
    - Garnett, Earle W., 1946-1947 (Box 17)
    - Gehman, William M., 1947-1954 (Box 17)
    - George, Walter F., 1949-1954 (Box 17)
    - George, William, 1951-1954 (Box 17)
    - Gifford, E. Garfield, 1948-1952 (Box 18)
    - Gillette, Guy M., 1952-1954 (Box 18)
    - Gloucester County (New Jersey) Bar Association, 1950-1957 (Box 18)
    - Gloucester County Clerk's Office, 1948-1954 (Box 18)
    - Gloucester County Historical Society, 1948-1951 (Box 18)
    - Gloucester County Probation Office, 1948-1954 (Box 18)
    - Gloucester County Republican Executive Committee, 1938-1964; 4 folders (Box 18)
    - Goldsmith, Howard C., 1947-1957 (Box 18)
    - Goldwater, Barry M., 1952-1961 (Box 18)
    - Goodwin, Angier, 1949 (Box 18)
    - Gore, Albert, 1952-1961 (Box 18)
    - Graham, Billy, 1952-1954 (Box 18)
    - Graham, Frank P., 1950-1952 (Box 18)
    - Green, Theodore Francis, 1952-1954 (Box 18)
    - Greenberg, Harry A., 1947-1948 (Box 18)
    - Grubb, Lily M., 1953-1954 (Box 18)
    - Gruber, Karl, 1954-1956 (Box 18)
    - Gumb, Irving, 1955-1961 (Box 18)
    - Grundy, Joseph Owen, 1939-1948 (Box 18)
    - Gurney, Chan, 1950 (Box 19)
    - Hab-Ham, 1937-1961 (Box 19)
    - Han-Han, 1942-1963 (Box 19)
    - Har-Har, 1937-1954 (Box 19)
    - Har-Hea, 1939-1954 (Box 19)
    - Her-Hit, 1938-1957 (Box 20)
    - Hoa-Hoo, 1942-1964 (Box 20)
    - Hop-How, 1941-1961 (Box 20)
    - Hoy-Hym, 1934-1963 (Box 20)
    - Hague, Frank, 1941-1942 (Box 20)
    - Haines, Charles H., 1955-1958 (Box 20)
    - Hancock, Howard, 1948 (Box 20)
    - Hand, Kenneth C., 1948-1953 (Box 20)
    - Hand T. Millet, 1946-1954 (Box 20)
    - Hannoch, Herbert, 1941-1951 (Box 20)
    - Hannold, Harold W., 1938-1957 (Box 21)
    - Hanrahan, William G., 1947-1948 (Box 21)
    - Harper and Brothers Publishing Company, 1953 (Box 21)
    - Hart, Edward J., 1949-1954 (Box 21)
    - Hartigan, John D., 1946-1958; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Hathaway, Edward N., 1955 (Box 21)
    - Hartshone, Richard, 1937-1959 (Box 21)
    - [Ira] Haupt and Company, 1942-1948 (Box 21)
    - Hawkes, Albert W., 1942-1953 (Box 21)
    - Hawkins, Delafield and Wood, 1938-1951 (Box 21)
    - Hayden, Carl, 1949-1962 (Box 21)
    - Heaton, Vivian, 1947-1960 (Box 21)
    - Henderson, Loy W., 1955-1956 (Box 21)
    - Hendrickson, Daniel J. P., 1939-1955; 4 folders (Box 22)
    - Hendrickson, Daniel J. P., 1956-1964; 3 folders (Box 23)
    - Hendrickson, F. Lynn, 1941-1963 (Box 23)
    - Hendrickson, Olga, 1943-1950 (Box 23)
    - Hendrickson, Robert C., 1940-1942 (Box 23)
    - Hendrickson, Robert C. Jr., 1945-1964 (Box 23)
    - Hendrickson, Sara P., 1962-1964 (Box 23)
    - Hendrickson Family, 1837-1956 (Box 23)
    - Hennings, Thomas C. Jr., 1951-1958 (Box 24)
    - Herbert, Stanley, 1946-1954 (Box 24)
    - Hermann, Albert B., 1945-1953 (Box 24)
    - Herr and Fischer, 1937-1954 (Box 24)
    - Herter, Christian A., 1960 (Box 24)
    - Hickenlooper, Bourke B., 1950-1956 (Box 24)
    - Higgins, William A., 1941 (Box 24)
    - Hilldring, J. H., 1946 (Box 24)
    - Holland, Spessard L., 1950-1956 (Box 24)
    - Holston, J. Sennett, 1943-1964 (Box 24)
    - Hood, Warren S., 1946-1948 (Box 24)
    - Hoover, Herbert, Jr., 1953-1956 (Box 24)
    - Hoover J. Edgar, 1951-1954 (Box 24)
    - Hopewell National Bank, Hopewell N.J., 1942-1948 (Box 24)
    - Horan, Eugene L., 1939-1953 (Box 24)
    - Hornstein, Isadore, 1946-1962 (Box 24)
    - Howell, Charles R., 1949-1954 (Box 24)
    - Hruska, Roman L., 1957 (Box 24)
    - Hudson County New Jersey, 1937-1950 (Box 24)
    - Hudson and Manhattan Railroad Company, 1941-1942 (Box 24)
    - Hudson News, 1938-1940 (Box 24)
    - Hudson Trust Company, 1942-1947 (Box 24)
    - Hull, Cordell, 1939 (Box 24)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1951-1959 (Box 24)
    - Hunt, Leigh, 1956-1964 (Box 24)
    - Hunt, Lester C., 1951-1954 (Box 24)
    - Ill-Ita, 1937-1952 (Box 24)
    - Ilott, John, 1955-1962 (Box 24)
    - Infantile Paralysis Fund Campaign, 1946 (Box 25)
    - International Christian Leadership, and International Council for Christian Leadership, 1949-1956 (Box 25)
    - Interstate Commission on Crime, 1941-1942 (Box 25)
    - Interstate Commission on the Delaware River Basin, 1937-1959; 6 folders (Box 25)
    - Irvington Varnish and Insulator Company, 1950-1951 (Box 25)
    - Ives, Irving M., 1949-1962 (Box 25)
    - Jac-Jer, 1937-1961 (Box 25)
    - Jer-Joh, 1939-1958 (Box 26)
    - Joh-Jus, 1937-1961 (Box 26)
    - Jameison, Crawford, 1939-1953 (Box 26)
    - Jenner, William E., 1948-1954 (Box 26)
    - Johnson, Edwin C., 1951-1964 (Box 26)
    - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1951-1964 (Box 26)
    - Johnson, Robert L., 1949-1961 (Box 26)
    - Johnson, Robert Wood, 1938-1961 (Box 26)
    - Johnson and Johnson, New Brunswick, N.J., 1949-1950 (Box 26)
    - Johnston, Eric, 1949-1953 (Box 26)
    - Johnston, Felton M., 1951 (Box 26)
    - Johnston, Olin D., 1950-1955 (Box 26)
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, 1953 (Box 26)
    - Joint Executive Committee for the Improvement and Development of the Philadelphia Port Area, 1949-1954 (Box 26)
    - Jones, Catesby L., 1948-1951 (Box 26)
    - Jones, Howard P., 1953-1961 (Box 26)
    - Jones, J. Webster, 1954 (Box 26)
    - Joyce, Louis C. Jr., 1939-1952 (Box 26)
    - Judd, Walter, 1955-1956 (Box 26)
    - Jurik, Maria, 1946-1949 (Box 26)
    - Kac-Kef, 1937-1961 (Box 27)
    - Kei-Ker, 1942-1951 (Box 27)
    - Kes-Kip, 1937-1958 (Box 27)
    - Kir-Klo, 1937-1957 (Box 27)
    - Kna-Kov, 1937-1962 (Box 27)
    - Kra-Kwa, 1937-1953 (Box 27)
    - Kanter, Elias A., 1941-1942 (Box 27)
    - Katchen, Julius, 1955 (Box 27)
    - Kavanaugh, John M., 1955-1958 (Box 27)
    - Kean, Robert W., 1948-1958 (Box 28)
    - Kefauver, Estes, 1949-1955 (Box 28)
    - Kelly, Frank S., 1938-1939 (Box 28)
    - Kem, James P., 1948-1951 (Box 28)
    - Kemper, James S., 1960 (Box 28)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1952-1954 (Box 28)
    - Kerney, James Jr., 1947-1952 (Box 28)
    - Kerr, Robert S., 1950-1954 (Box 28)
    - Keruse, Stephen, 1962-1964 (Box 28)
    - Kieb, Ormonde A., 1956-1957 (Box 28)
    - Kiefer, Homer W., 1952 (Box 28)
    - Kierner, William F., 1951 (Box 28)
    - Kilgore, Harley M., 1951-1954 (Box 28)
    - King, Reuben R., 1951-1954 (Box 28)
    - Klaisz, R. Edward, 1938-1964 (Box 28)
    - Klein, Alfred M., 1953 (Box 28)
    - Knowland, William F., 1949-1958 (Box 28)
    - Kotz, Howard and Mary, 1949-1959 (Box 28)
    - Kuebler, Paul Charles, 1947-1948 (Box 28)
    - Laboon, John F., 1945-1948 (Box 28)
    - Lab-Lar, 1938-1954 (Box 28)
    - Las-Led, 1937-1963 (Box 28)
    - Lee-Lev, 1937-1955 (Box 28)
    - Lew-Lio, 1942-1959 (Box 29)
    - Lip-Lon, 1939-1958 (Box 29)
    - Lor-Lou, 1937-1952 (Box 29)
    - Lov-Lus, 1941-1959 (Box 29)
    - Langer, William, 1951-1954 (Box 29)
    - Larcombe, J. Russel, 1938-1964 (Box 29)
    - Lawrence, Robert L., 1955-1956 (Box 29)
    - Lawson, Alexander R., 1948-1962 (Box 29)
    - Lawson Robert S. 0., 1943-1948 (Box 29)
    - League of Women Voters of New Jersey, 1947-1959 (Box 30)
    - Lee, O. Pierre, 1948-1956 (Box 30)
    - Lehigh Railroad Company, 1941-1942 (Box 30)
    - Lehman, Herbert H., 1951-1952 (Box 30)
    - Lend-Lease Administration Office, 1942 (Box 30)
    - Levy, Joseph W., 1942-1961 (Box 30)
    - Lewis, Arthur W., 1946-1961 (Box 30)
    - Liakas, Elias, 1949-1957 (Box 30)
    - Linke, Julian P., 1952 (Box 30)
    - Lindsay, John V., 1955 (Box 30)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1948-1953 (Box 30)
    - Logan James A., 1938-1946 (Box 30)
    - Loizeaux, Charles E., 1938-1943 (Box 30)
    - Long, Russell B., 1949-1954 (Box 30)
    - Lourie, Samuel Anatole, 1951 (Box 30)
    - Lowe, Donald V., 1941-1948 (Box 30)
    - Lucas, Scott W., 1950-1954 (Box 30)
    - Luce, Claire Booth, 1953 (Box 30)
    - Lukashewich, Olga, 1955-1960 (Box 30)
    - Lum, Ralph E., 1941-1942 (Box 30)
    - Lynn, David, 1949 (Box 30)
    - Mac-Mac, 1943-1956 (Box 30)
    - McA-McE, 1942-1958 (Box 30)
    - McF-McS, 1936-1957 (Box 30)
    - Mac-Mag, 1941-1955 (Box 31)
    - Mah-Mar, 1942-1959 (Box 31)
    - Mar-May, 1939-1956 (Box 31)
    - Mea-Mer, 1937-1958 (Box 31)
    - Mer-Mid, 1938-1960 (Box 31)
    - Mie-Mil, 1938-1956 (Box 31)
    - Min-Mon, 1942-1961 (Box 31)
    - Moo-Mor, 1941-1964 (Box 32)
    - Mor-Mun, 1937-1959 (Box 32)
    - Mur-Myr, 1938-1963 (Box 32)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, 1951-1957 (Box 32)
    - Macfarlane, Ivor H., 1939-1960 (Box 32)
    - McCaffree, Mary Jane, 1957 (Box 32)
    - McCampbell, Theron, 1940-1944 (Box 32)
    - McCarran, Pat, 1949-1954 (Box 32)
    - McCarter, English and Studer, 1947-1954 (Box 32)
    - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1951-1954 (Box 32)
    - McClellan, John L., 1957 (Box 32)
    - McCraith, Charles E., 1942-1948 (Box 32)
    - McCrary, Tex and Jinx Falkenburg, 1954 (Box 32)
    - McFarland, Ernest W., 1949-1951 (Box 32)
    - McGeehan, John B., 1939-1948 (Box 32)
    - McGraith, Howard, 1951 (Box 32)
    - McGraw-Hill Publishing Company, 1948-1951 (Box 32)
    - McKee, Frank S., 1946-1949 (Box 32)
    - McMahon, Brien, 1950-1951 (Box 33)
    - McManus, Robert Cruise, 1941-1953 (Box 33)
    - Mack, Ted, 1951 (Box 33)
    - Mackay, R. W. G., 1951 (Box 33)
    - Magee, Arthur, 1938-1940 (Box 33)
    - Magnuson, Warren G., 1950-1954 (Box 33)
    - Malone, George W., 1948-1954 (Box 33)
    - Mandel, Benjamin, 1953-1954 (Box 33)
    - Mansfield, Mike, 1952-1954 (Box 33)
    - Marsh, Lloyd B., 1943-1951 (Box 33)
    - Martin, Edward, 1942-1957 (Box 33)
    - Martin, J. H. Thayer, 1938-1953 (Box 33)
    - Martine, Leroy M., 1950 (Box 33)
    - Mazengarb, Oswald C., 1955-1956 (Box 33)
    - Meadows, Nathan R., 1955-1958 (Box 33)
    - Megary, William M., 1947-1952 (Box 33)
    - Mehorter, Hugh L., 1939-1964 (Box 33)
    - Mehorter, Samuel A., 1943-1955 (Box 33)
    - Melniker, Aaron A., 1937-1955 (Box 33)
    - Mennite, Joseph, 1950-1953 (Box 33)
    - Mercer County (New Jersey) Clerk's Office, 1951-1954 (Box 33)
    - Mercer County Republican Committee, 1950-1954 (Box 33)
    - Meyner, Robert B., 1957-1961 (Box 33)
    - Military Government Association, 1947-1954 (Box 33)
    - Miller, Albert F.
      - 1941 Jan-Aug (Box 33)
      - 1941 Sep-1948 (Box 34)
    - Miller, Morris, 1949-1953 (Box 34)
    - Miller, Spencer Jr., 1943-1950 (Box 34)
    - Miller, William A., 1939-1951 (Box 34)
    - Millikin, Eugene D., 1948-1954 (Box 34)
    - Milton, Hugh M. II, 1955 (Box 34)
    - Minard, Duane E., 1942-1952 (Box 34)
    - Mitchell, C. Bayard II, 1957-1960 (Box 34)
    - Mitchell, James P., 1955 (Box 34)
    - Moody, Blair, 1951-1952 (Box 34)
    - Moore, Hervey S., 1938-1949 (Box 34)
    - Moran, Viola, 1955-1956 (Box 34)
    - Morris, Robert, 1953-1963 (Box 34)
    - Morse, David A., 1952-1958 (Box 34)
    - Morse, Wayne, 1950-1951 (Box 34)
    - Mudd, Arthur, 1938 (Box 34)
    - Mudge, Vernon, 1955 (Box 34)
    - Mundt, Karl E., 1950-1955 (Box 34)
    - Munro, Leslie, 1955-1957 (Box 34)
    - Murray, Frank J., 1938-1940 (Box 34)
    - Murray, James E., 1955-1966 (Box 34)
    - Musmanno, Michael A., 1938-1960 (Box 34)
    - Myers, Herbert F. Jr., 1942-1953 (Box 34)
    - Nac-Nat, 1939-1955 (Box 34)
    - Nat-Nat, 1948-1963 (Box 34)
    - Nat-Nav, 1950-1964 (Box 34)
    - Nea-New, 1939-1954 (Box 35)
    - New-Nyb, 1938-1963 (Box 35)
    - Nash, Walter, 1959-1961 (Box 35)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1949-1953 (Box 35)
    - National Association of Postmasters, 1950-1954 (Box 35)
    - National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers and Treasurers, 1947-1953 (Box 35)
    - National Banks of New Jersey, 1942-1954 (Box 35)
    - National Civil Service Reform League, 1941 (Box 35)
    - National Committee for Support of the Public Schools, 1962-1964 (Box 35)
    - National Draft MacArthur Committee, 1952 (Box 35)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1953-1954 (Box 35)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1949-1954 (Box 35)
    - National Meteorological Disaster Defense and Investigation Council, 1954 (Box 35)
    - National Municipal League, 1943-1959 (Box 35)
    - National Republican Club, 1948-1953 (Box 35)
    - Nester, Alfred T., 1952 (Box 35)
    - New Jersey
      - Miscellaneous associations and state agencies
        - Association-Council, 1937-1954 (Box 35)
        - Daughters-Hospital, 1937-1956 (Box 36)
        - Institute-Rifle, 1937-1959 (Box 36)
        - Savings-State Dental, 1938-1958 (Box 36)
        - State Federation-Young, 1937-1954 (Box 36)
      - Agricultural Experiment Stations, 1947-1954 (Box 36)
      - American Federation of Labor, 1942 (Box 36)
      - Association of Real Estate Boards, 1942-1949 (Box 36)
      - Bankers Association, 1938-1954 (Box 36)
      - Bar Association, 1937-1960 (Box 36)
      - Board of Pharmacy, 1942-1948 (Box 36)
      - Board of Public Utilities Commissioners, 1937-1946 (Box 36)
      - Chamber of Commerce, 1941-1963 (Box 36)
      - Civil Service Commission, 1938-1942 (Box 36)
      - Commission on Interstate Cooperation, 1937-1950 (Box 37)
      - Commission on Revision of the New Jersey Constitution, 1941-1948 (Box 37)
      - Commission on Statutes, 1941-1943 (Box 37)
      - Committee for Constitutional Convention, 1941-1947 (Box 37)
      - Committee for Polish Relief, 1940 (Box 37)
      - Constitutional Convention Association, 1951-1963 (Box 37)
      - Council of Christian Churches, 1952 (Box 37)
      - Democratic State Committee, 1940 (Box 37)
      - Department of Agriculture, 1947-1953 (Box 37)
      - Department of Banking and Insurance, 1942-1954 (Box 37)
      - Department of Conservation and Development, 1938-1954 (Box 37)
      - Department of Defense, 1942-1954 (Box 37)
      - Department of Economic Development, 1946-1952 (Box 37)
      - Department of Education, 1946-1962 (Box 37)
      - Department of Institutions and Agencies, 1942-1954 (Box 37)
      - Department of Labor, 1941-1951 (Box 37)
      - Department of Law and Public Safety, 1948-1954 (Box 37)
      - Department of Weights and Measures, 1938-1948 (Box 37)
      - Department of Taxation and Finance, 1946-1954 (Box 37)
      - Employees' Retirement System, 1938-1948 (Box 37)
      - Highway Department, 1937-1952 (Box 37)
      - League of Municipalities, 1937-1964 (Box 38)
      - Legislature's Bonus Commission, 1946-1949 (Box 38)
      - Military District, 1955 (Box 38)
      - Motor Vehicle Department, 1937-1961 (Box 38)
      - Municipal Aid Administrator, 1941-1942 (Box 38)
      - Office of the State Auditor, 1942-1948 (Box 38)
      - Office of the State Treasurer, 1942-1957 (Box 38)
      - Planning Boardq, 1941 (Box 38)
      - Republican State Committee, 1939-1962 (Box 38)
      - Republican Executive Finance Committee, 1948-1960 (Box 38)
      - Sinking Fund Commission, 1948 (Box 38)
      - State Patrolmens' Benevolent Association, 1939-1954 (Box 38)
      - State Tax Department, 1937-1942 (Box 38)
      - Taxpayers' Association, 1938-1954 (Box 38)
      - Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1938-1949 (Box 38)
      - World's Fair Commission, 1939 (Box 38)
      - New York, Susquehanna and Western Railroad Company, 1941-1954 (Box 38)
    - Newark, N.J., 1939-1954 (Box 39)
    - Newell, Forrest C., 1949 (Box 39)
    - Newsweek, 1952-1955 (Box 39)
    - New Zealand-American Association, 1957-1961 (Box 39)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1951-1960 (Box 39)
    - Noce, Daniel, 1947-1954 (Box 39)
    - Nolte, Donald, 1950-1963 (Box 39)
    - North American Airlines, 1954 (Box 39)
    - Norton, Mary T., 1933-1949 (Box 39)
    - Nyburg, Willard L. and Olga, 1946-1962 (Box 39)
    - Oat-Ols, 1946-1954 (Box 39)
    - O'Ma-Oxf, 1942-1959 (Box 39)
    - O'Brien, Lawrence F., 1963 (Box 39)
    - Old Guard, City of Philadelphia Inc., 1953-1958 (Box 39)
    - Olson, Ann M., 1953-1958 (Box 39)
    - O'Mahoney Joseph C., 1949 (Box 39)
    - Orben, C. Milford, 1941-1948 (Box 39)
    - Osmers, Frank, 1939-1961 (Box 39)
    - Ostertag, Harold C., 1941-1950 (Box 39)
    - Paa-Par, 1937-1959 (Box 39)
    - Par-Pay, 1937-1954 (Box 39)
    - Pea-Per, 1942-1964 (Box 39)
    - Per-Pez, 1949-1959 (Box 40)
    - Pfe-Phi, 1938-1961 (Box 40)
    - Pic-Pit, 1937-1959 (Box 40)
    - Pla-Por, 1939-1959 (Box 40)
    - Pos-Pow, 1939-1959 (Box 40)
    - Pra-Pry, 1939-1955 (Box 40)
    - Pub-Pyn, 1940-1963 (Box 40)
    - Palmieri, Edmund L., 1948-1955 (Box 40)
    - Parsons, Theodore D., 1949-1953 (Box 40)
    - Pascoe, Herbert J., 1938-1948 (Box 40)
    - Paterson Evening News, 1946-1954 (Box 40)
    - Paul, Joseph C., 1940-1950 (Box 41)
    - Paul, Winston, 1943-1952 (Box 41)
    - Payne, Frederick K., 1953 (Box 41)
    - Peaslee, Amos J., 1946-1959 (Box 41)
    - Penn Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1946-1959 (Box 41)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1939-1957 (Box 41)
    - Pennsylvania-Reading Seashore Lines, 1939-1947 (Box 41)
    - Peterson, Henry W., 1940-1958 (Box 41)
    - Philadelphia Penn., 1949-1959 (Box 41)
    - Pickering, W. B., 1938-1958 (Box 41)
    - Pierson, Arthur N., 1938-1948 (Box 41)
    - Powers, D. Lane, 1941-1954 (Box 41)
    - Prentice-Hall Inc., 1959 (Box 41)
    - Prescott, John Parker, 1953-1957 (Box 41)
    - Price, Mark, 1961 (Box 41)
    - Prickett, Clarence D., 1947-1964 (Box 41)
    - Princeton University, 1939-1953 (Box 41)
    - Proctor, Haydn, 1939-1951 (Box 42)
    - Purtell, William A., 1952-1956 (Box 42)
    - Pyro Plastics Corporation, 1953-1954 (Box 42)
    - Quackenbush, Granville A., 1943-1957 (Box 42)
    - Raa-Ray, 1942-1963 (Box 42)
    - Rea-Rei, 1937-1955 (Box 42)
    - Rei-Rif, 1937-1955 (Box 42)
    - Rig-Roe, 1937-1954 (Box 42)
    - Rog-Rot, 1937-1954 (Box 42)
    - Rot-Ryk, 1947-1961 (Box 43)
    - Ralston, Wayne M., 1946-1963 (Box 43)
    - Rathblott, Albert, 1953-1954 (Box 43)
    - Redding, George A., 1947-1948 (Box 43)
    - Reichenstein, Harry S., 1950-1964 (Box 43)
    - Republican National Committee, 1948-1964 (Box 43)
    - Reserve Officers Association of the U.S., 1949-1957 (Box 43)
    - Rey, Harry Robert, 1943-1950 (Box 43)
    - Reynolds & Co., 1942-1947 (Box 43)
    - Richardson, Ralph G., 1941-1943 (Box 43)
    - Rigging, Albert J., 1946-1957 (Box 43)
    - Rippel, Julius A., 1942-1948 (Box 43)
    - Roberson, Horace K., 1937-1952 (Box 43)
    - Robertson, A. Willis, 1949-1954 (Box 43)
    - Robertson, Walter S., 1956-1957 (Box 43)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1953-1960 (Box 43)
    - Roebling, Mary G., 1947-1963 (Box 43)
    - Roesti, Max F., 1947-1953 (Box 43)
    - Rogers, Leslie W., 1946-1962 (Box 43)
    - Rogers, William P., 1953-1958 (Box 43)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1951 (Box 43)
    - Rothman, S., 1955-1956 (Box 43)
    - Russell, Francis H., 1957-1959 (Box 43)
    - Russell, Richard B., 1951-1956 (Box 43)
    - Rutgers University, 1938-1953 (Box 44)
    - Sab-Say, 1938-1961 (Box 44)
    - Sca-Sch, 1941-1962 (Box 44)
    - Sch-Scr, 1939-1955 (Box 44)
    - Sea-Sgo, 1937-1956 (Box 44)
    - Sha-She, 1938-1954 (Box 45)
    - She-She, 1937-1956 (Box 45)
    - Sib-Sil, 1937-1956 (Box 45)
    - Sim-Siz, 1937-1952 (Box 45)
    - Ska-Sko, 1937-1953 (Box 45)
    - Sla-Sly, 1937-1954 (Box 45)
    - Sma-Smy, 1937-1954 (Box 45)
    - Sne-Sny, 1943-1953 (Box 45)
    - Soc-Sow, 1940-1963 (Box 45)
    - Spa-Spr, 1941-1963 (Box 45)
    - St. A-Sta, 1937-1955 (Box 46)
    - Ste-Ste, 1942-1954 (Box 46)
    - Ste-Ste, 1939-1959 (Box 46)
    - Sti-Sto, 1938-1962 (Box 46)
    - Str-Str, 1942-1963 (Box 46)
    - Stu-Sty, 1948-1961 (Box 46)
    - Sub-Suy, 1946-1964 (Box 46)
    - Swa-Swi, 1941-1958 (Box 46)
    - Syk-Sym, 1938-1956 (Box 46)
    - Sabatino, Louis A., 1946-1964; 3 folders (Box 47)
    - Saltonstall, Leverett, 1949-1954 (Box 47)
    - The Salvation Army, 1947-1964 (Box 47)
    - Sarnoff, David, 1948 (Box 47)
    - Saul, Walter Biddle, 1946-1954 (Box 47)
    - Schlesinger, Joel L., 1951-1961 (Box 47)
    - Schoeppel, Andrew F., 1957 (Box 48)
    - Seaton, Fred A., 1957 (Box 48)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1952 (Box 48)
    - Senate Armed Services Committee, 1953 (Box 48)
    - Seventeenth Ward Club, 1948 (Box 48)
    - Sholl, John G., 1943-1955 (Box 48)
    - Singh, Tara, 1951-1953 (Box 48)
    - Sirota, Nathan H., 1947-1955 (Box 48)
    - Skillman, George G., 1941-1954 (Box 48)
    - Smidley, Clarence E., 1946-1948 (Box 48)
    - Smith, H. Alexander, 1939-1961; 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Smith, Carl V., 1955-1956 (Box 48)
    - Smith, Elaine D., 1955-1956 (Box 48)
    - Smith, Margaret Chase, 1951-1963 (Box 48)
    - Smith, Willis, 1951-1953 (Box 48)
    - Snook, Russell A., 1945-1963 (Box 49)
    - Snyder, Howard, 1956-1957 (Box 49)
    - Sobell, Helen, 1954-1955 (Box 49)
    - Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, 1941-1954 (Box 49)
    - Society of the Cincinnati in the State of New Jersey, 1949-1959 (Box 49)
    - Somerset County (New Jersey) Historical Society, 1953-1955 (Box 49)
    - South Jersey Port Commission, 1946-1953 (Box 49)
    - Sparkman, John J., 1950-1954 (Box 49)
    - Spears, Mrs. William H., 1950-1955; 2 folders (Box 49)
      The second folder contains photocopied letters; some, but not all, are duplicates of letters in the first folder.
    - Springer, Elizabeth B., 1950-1953 (Box 49)
    - Stassen, Harold, 1955 (Box 49)
    - State Society of the Battleship New Jersey, 1944-1952 (Box 49)
    - Steineder, R. J., 1947 (Box 49)
    - Stennis, John C., 1955-1956 (Box 49)
    - Stewart, Raymond J., 1949-1950 (Box 49)
    - Stichel, Fred G., Jr., 1942-1954 (Box 49)
    - Storrie, William R., 1939-1943 (Box 49)
    - Stout, Richard W., 1942-1954 (Box 49)
    - Strain, Eric, 1955-1956 (Box 49)
    - Struble, Clyde W., 1947-1948 (Box 49)
    - Stryker, Tams and Horner, 1945-1951 (Box 49)
    - Suburban Homes Building and Loan Association of Woodbury, N.J.
      - 1923-1931, 3 folders (Box 49)
      - 1942-1960 (Box 50)
    - Summerfield, Arthur E., 1955-1958 (Box 50)
    - Summerhill, John M. Jr., 1938-1948 (Box 50)
    - Swedesboro Trust Company, 1943-1948 (Box 50)
    - Symington, Stuart, 1952-1955 (Box 50)
    - T-Ten, 1937-1964 (Box 50)
    - Ten-Thu, 1937-1960 (Box 50)
    - Tie-Ton, 1948-1955 (Box 50)
    - Too-Tri, 1937-1961 (Box 50)
    - Tri-Tys, 1937-1963 (Box 50)
    - Taft, Robert A., 1950-1953 (Box 51)
    - Taggart, Thomas D. Jr., 1937-1938 (Box 51)
    - Tate, Marion S., 1946-1947 (Box 51)
    - Taylor, Harry A., 1937-1952 (Box 51)
    - Television Code Review Board, 1954 (Box 51)
    - Temple, Ralph R., 1947-1948 (Box 51)
    - Temple University, 1940-1964; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Tilghman, M. T., 1951 (Box 51)
    - Thompson, Geraldine L., 1942-1954 (Box 51)
    - Thompson, Mary I., 1942-1951 (Box 51)
    - Thye, Edward J., 1949-1954 (Box 51)
    - Tien Fang Cheng, 1955-1956 (Box 51)
    - Tobey, Charles W., 1950-1951 (Box 51)
    - Towe, Harry L., 1942-1954 (Box 51)
    - Todd, Webster B., 1948-1961 (Box 51)
    - Trenton Banking Company, 1942-1946 (Box 51)
    - Trenton Times, 1942-1958 (Box 51)
    - Trenton Trust Company, 1942-1946 (Box 51)
    - Trice, J. Mark, 1948-1953 (Box 51)
    - Troast, Paul L., 1953 (Box 51)
    - Truman, Harry S, 1950-1952 (Box 51)
    - Turpanjian, M. Martin, 1955 (Box 51)
    - Uni-Uni, 1938-1954 (Box 51)
    - Uni-Urg, 1938-1956 (Box 51)
    - United Auto Workers, 1953-1954 (Box 52)
    - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1949-1954 (Box 52)
    - United Properties, 1945-1956 (Box 52)
    - United Services Organizations, 1952-1962 (Box 52)
    - United States
      - Civil Service Commission, 1943-1958 (Box 52)
      - Coast Guard Auxiliary, 1941-1958 (Box 52)
      - Department of the Air Force, 1949-1954 (Box 52)